# Grzegorz Pasich



Hi, my name is Grzesiek, I am student of third year IT on Crakow University of Technology. I'm interested in programming and IT field for three years that's why i study IT.

I work as an International forwarder on a daily basis, that's why working with work staff is familiar to me, I know what is teamwork and i like work with others people.

I like solving various problems, my strengths are creativity, communicativeness, independence and good organization of work and achieving the set purposes.

I would like to start developing in my target profession in IT field, that's why I am submitting an application to your company because in my opinion work and gaining experience is the best form of gaining knowledge and skills.

## Personal data

### **Address**

ul. Dębowa 10

32-340 Wolbrom

Małopolskie

### **Email**

grzegorz.pasich@o2.pl

### Phone number

+48 608 158 611

### Languages

Polish – native

English - B2

## Experience

### Software pcb tester

Inex, Katowice

2019-03 - 2019-06

- Realization of orders on time with a team of 4.
- The work consisted in uploading the software to a pcb board, checking the correctness of the uploaded software.

### **International forwarder**

Marcin Pałka, Wolbrom 2020-08 - 2021-07

Trans4, Wolbrom 2021-10 – 2022-06

FTUH Paweł Broczkowski, Wolbrom 2022-06 - until now

- Contacting foreign clients in a foreign language.
- Active acquisition of transport orders.
- Taking care of the high level of provided transport services.
- Preparation of shipping documentation.
- Transport process flow control.
- Planning of transport orders.
- Provision of appropriate means of transport to fulfill customer orders.
- Solving problems arising during the transport process.
- Building proper relationships with customers and carriers.
- Ensuring the correct flow of information and documents.

### **Skills**

- ✓ C/C++
- ✓ Python
- ✓ HTML
- ✓ CSS
- ✓ JavaScript
- ✓ Git
- ✓ Linux
- ✓ Docker
- ✓ React
- ✓ Adobe Photoshop
- ✓ Knowledge SQL
- ✓ Microsoft Office
- ✓ Ability to work under stress
- ✓ Responsibility for the implementation of entrusted tasks
- ✓ Ability to think analytically
- ✓ Communicativeness
- ✓ Ability to work in a team
- ✓ Creativity
- ✓ Independence and good organization of work
- ✓ Ability to accurately define priorities
- ✓ Achieving the set goals.

## Education

**High School** 2015-09 – 2018-04

I High School name's Kazimierz Wielki Poland, Olkusz

JavaScript Course 2023-04

Inventum Sp. z o. o. Poland, Nowy Sacz

## IT, Engineering Studies

2020-10 - until now

Crakow University of Technology, Crakow Faculty of Computer Science and Telecomunications